[{"question": "\u0427\u0442\u043e \u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0435 Python?", "options": ["\u042f\u0437\u044b\u043a \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0440\u0430\u043c\u043c\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044f", "\u0422\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445", "\u041c\u0443\u0437\u044b\u043a\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442", "\u0417\u043c\u0435\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u0430\u043d\u0433\u043b\u0438\u0439\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043c"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0442\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0446\u0435\u043b\u044b\u0445 \u0447\u0438\u0441\u0435\u043b?", "options": ["int", "float", "str", "natural"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u0427\u0435\u043c \u0437\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0448\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043e\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0440 if", "options": ["for", "while", "elif", "else"], "correct_option": 3}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0437\u043d\u0430\u043a \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0432 \u0441\u0442\u0435\u043f\u0435\u043d\u044c?", "options": ["+", "-", "*", "**"], "correct_option": 3}, {"question": "\u0421\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e \u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0446\u0438\u043a\u043b\u043e\u0432 \u0432 \u044f\u0437\u044b\u043a\u0435 Python?", "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"], "correct_option": 1}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a \u043d\u0430\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043e\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0440 \u0444\u0443\u043d\u043a\u0446\u0438\u0438?", "options": ["set", "a", "def", "str"], "correct_option": 2}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0442\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442 \u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u0443\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0435 \u0441\u043a\u043e\u0431\u043a\u0438 []", "options": ["dict", "list", "str", "set"], "correct_option": 1}, {"question": "\u0427\u0442\u043e \u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0435 NumPy", "options": ["\u0444\u0443\u043d\u043a\u0446\u0438\u044f", "\u0431\u0438\u0431\u043b\u0438\u043e\u0442\u0435\u043a\u0430", "\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d\u043d\u0430\u044f", "\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u0442\u0430"], "correct_option": 1}, {"question": "\u043a\u0430\u043a\u0438\u043c \u043c\u0435\u0442\u043e\u0434\u043e\u043c \u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e \u0434\u043e\u0431\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c \u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0439 \u0432 \u043a\u0430\u0432\u044b\u0447\u043a\u0438 \u043d\u0435 \u0437\u0430\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0432\u0430\u044f \u0438\u0445?", "options": ["f", "q", "w", "z"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u043a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0435 \u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0439 \u0431\u0443\u0434\u0435\u0442 \u0432  z = 3**2", "options": ["27", "0", "9", "6"], "correct_option": 2}]